A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), Series 9 FA1721
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), 1997-2006; 9; 52.57 Cubic Feet
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 4901-5034 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 4901-5034 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 5036-5095 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 5036-5095 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 5036-5095 (Box 18)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 18)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 18)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 18)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 18)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 18)
  - University of Iowa, WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 19)
  - University of Iowa, WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 19)
  - University of Iowa, WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 19)
  - University of Iowa, WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 19)
  - University of Iowa, WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 3202-3459 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 3202-3459 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 3202-3459 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 3553-3842 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 3553-3842 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 3553-3842 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 3855-4180 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 3855-4180 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 3855-4180 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 4218-41973 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 4218-41973 (Box 19)
  - Virginia, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 4218-41973 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101885-101930 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101885-101930 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101885-101930 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101885-101930 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101885-101930 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101931-101982 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101931-101982 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101931-101982 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101931-101982 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101931-101982 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101985-102041 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101985-102041 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101985-102041 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101985-102041 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101985-102041 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 102042-102087 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 102042-102087 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 102042-102087 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 102042-102087 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 102042-102087 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 102132-102211 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 102132-102211 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 102132-102211 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 102132-102211 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 102042-102087 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 102212-102284 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 102212-102284 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 102212-102284 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 102212-102284 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 102212-102284 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 102088-102131 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 102088-102131 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 102088-102131 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 102088-102131 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Mason Medical, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 102088-102131 (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 1042xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 1042xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 1042xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 1042xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 1042xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 1092xx-1099xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 1092xx-1099xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 1092xx-1099xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 1092xx-1099xx (Box 20)
  - WA Foote Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 1092xx-1099xx (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 104170-104566 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 104568-104675 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 104770-105019 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1, 105020-105215 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 104170-104566 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 104568-104675 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 104770-105019 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 105020-105215 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 104170-104566 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 104568-104675 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 104770-105019 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 105020-105215 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 104170-104566 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 104568-104675 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 104770-105019 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 105020-105215 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 104170-104566 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 104568-104675 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 104770-105019 (Box 20)
  - Kaleida Health, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 105020-105215 (Box 20)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 2330-23378 (Box 20)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 2330-23378 (Box 20)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 2330-23378 (Box 20)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 23379-23438 (Box 20)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 23379-23438 (Box 20)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 23379-23438 (Box 20)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 23439-23821 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 23439-23821 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 23439-23821 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 23822-23910 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 23822-23910 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 23822-23910 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 23912-24002 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 23912-24002 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 23912-24002 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 24003-24063 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 24003-24063 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 24003-24063 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 24064-25107 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 24064-25107 (Box 21)
  - Koot, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 24064-25107 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 1-2, 0002-0061 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 3-4, 0002-0061 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 5-6, 0002-0061 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 7, 0002-0061 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 1-2, 0062-00129 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 3-4, 0062-00129 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 5-6, 0062-00129 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 7, 0062-00129 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 1-2, 00130-0200 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 3-4, 00130-0200 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 5-6, 00130-0200 (Box 21)
  - Maine Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V3, Page 7, 00130-0200 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1401-1488 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1401-1488 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1401-1488 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1492-1741 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1492-1741 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1492-1741 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1742-1777 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1742-1777 (Box 21)
  - Martha Jefferson, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1742-1777 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center of Ocean County, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center of Ocean County, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center of Ocean County, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center of Ocean County, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center of Ocean County, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 21)
  - Heart Stone & Genesis, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 22)
  - Heart Stone & Genesis, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 22)
  - Heart Stone & Genesis, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 22)
  - Heart Stone & Genesis, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 22)
  - Heart Stone & Genesis, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 22)
  - INOVA Fairfax Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 22)
  - INOVA Fairfax Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 22)
  - INOVA Fairfax Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 22)
  - INOVA Fairfax Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 22)
  - INOVA Fairfax Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 22)
  - Jersey Shore Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 22)
  - Jersey Shore Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 23)
  - Jersey Shore Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 23)
  - Jersey Shore Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 23)
  - Jersey Shore Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 23)